(function(){var e={3762:function(e,t,n){"use strict";var a=n(5471),o=n(4302),r=n.n(o),i=n(6093),s=function(){var e=this,t=e._self._c;return t("Experiment",{attrs:{title:"indicom"}},[t("InstructionScreen",{attrs:{title:"Welcome"}},[t("p",[e._v("Thank you for taking part in this study.")]),t("p",[e._v("In this experiment, you will be shown small fictional dialogues each consisting of a context sentence, a question and an answer.")]),t("p",[e._v("Your task is to read the scenario carefully and to rate whether you think the answer given to the question means “no” or “yes” on a scale from 1 (“definitely no”) to 7 (“definitely yes”).")]),t("p",[e._v("You must read all information presented with each scenario. There will be attention checks, which ask you to give a specific rating. ")])]),e._l(e.sampledTriples,function(n,a){return[e._l(n,function(n,o){return[t("Screen",{key:"t"+a+"_i"+o,attrs:{progress:(4*a+o+1)/e.totalScreens}},[t("Slide",[t("div",{staticClass:"context-box"},[t("p",[e._v(e._s(n.contextsentence))])]),t("p",[t("b",[e._v(e._s(n.speaker1)+":")]),e._v(" "+e._s(n.polarquestion))]),t("p",[t("b",[e._v(e._s(n.speaker2)+":")]),e._v(" "+e._s(n.indirectanswer))]),t("p",{staticClass:"question-block"},[e._v(" Does "+e._s(n.speaker2)+"’s reply mean “no” or “yes”? ")]),t("RatingInput",{attrs:{left:"definitely no",response:e.$magpie.measurements.rating,right:"definitely yes"},on:{"update:response":function(t){return e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"rating",t)}}}),void 0!==e.$magpie.measurements.rating&&null!==e.$magpie.measurements.rating?t("p",[t("button",{on:{click:function(t){return e.$magpie.saveAndNextScreen()}}},[e._v("Submit")])]):e._e(),t("div",{staticClass:"comment-container"},[t("label",{staticClass:"comment-label"},[e._v(" Comments (optional): ")]),t("textarea",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.$magpie.measurements["comment_"+a+"_"+o],expression:"$magpie.measurements['comment_' + tIndex + '_' + i]"}],staticClass:"comment-box",attrs:{placeholder:"If anything was unclear or you have any feedback, you can leave it here."},domProps:{value:e.$magpie.measurements["comment_"+a+"_"+o]},on:{input:function(t){t.target.composing||e.$set(e.$magpie.measurements,"comment_"+a+"_"+o,t.target.value)}}})]),t("Record",{attrs:{data:{trialType:n.trialType,key:"trial_"+a+"_"+o,itemID:n.Item,contextType:n["Context Type"],rating:e.$magpie.measurements.rating,comment:e.$magpie.measurements["comment"]||null,speaker1:n.speaker1,speaker2:n.speaker2}}})],1)],1)]})]}),t("PostTestScreen"),t("SubmitResultsScreen")],2)},l=[],p=n(3913),c=n.n(p),d=n(5851),u=n.n(d),h=n(2543),m=n.n(h);const y=c().map(e=>({...e,Item:Number(e["Item"]),"Context Type":e["Context Type"].trim().toLowerCase()})),k=u().map(e=>({...e,"Context Type":e["Context Type"].trim().toLowerCase()})),w=["positive","negative","neutral"],g=m().range(1,31),v=m().sampleSize(g,9),x=m().chunk(v,3),f=x.map((e,t)=>{const n=m().shuffle(w),a=e.map((e,t)=>{const a=n[t],o=y.find(t=>t.Item===e&&t["Context Type"]===a);return o||null});a.forEach(e=>e.trialType="main");const o=k[t%k.length];return o.trialType="attention",a.push(o),a});console.log("RESULT sampledTriples:",f);var b={name:"App",data(){return{sampledIDs:v,triples:x,sampledTriples:f,screensPerTriple:4,attentionChecks:u()}},computed:{_(){return m()},totalScreens(){return this.sampledTriples.length*this.screensPerTriple}}},T=b,I=n(1656),C=(0,I.A)(T,s,l,!1,null,null,null),S=C.exports,q={experimentId:"37",serverUrl:"https://magpie-cogsciprag.fly.dev",socketUrl:"wss://magpie-cogsciprag.fly.dev/socket",completionUrl:"https://app.prolific.com/submissions/complete?cc=C2VG26QB",contactEmail:"michael.franke@uni-tuebingen.de",mode:"directLink",language:"en"};a["default"].config.productionTip=!1,a["default"].use(r(),{prefix:"Canvas"}),a["default"].use(i.Ay,q),new a["default"]({render:e=>e(S)}).$mount("#app")},3913:function(e){e.exports=[{Item:1,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"John",speaker2:"Mary",contextsentence:"John and Mary are windsurfers and regularly surf together.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the beach today?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s windy.”"},{Item:1,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"John",speaker2:"Mary",contextsentence:"John and Mary want to tan at the beach together.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the beach today?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s windy.”"},{Item:1,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"John",speaker2:"Mary",contextsentence:"John and Mary are talking about going to the beach.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the beach today?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s windy.”"},{Item:2,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Alex",speaker2:"Bo",contextsentence:"Alex and Bo are celebrating their 10th anniversary and want to treat themselves.",polarquestion:"“Should we book that restaurant?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s expensive.”"},{Item:2,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Alex",speaker2:"Bo",contextsentence:"Alex and Bo are on a budget and want to have a cheap dinner out.",polarquestion:"“Should we book that restaurant?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s expensive.”"},{Item:2,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Alex",speaker2:"Bo",contextsentence:"Alex and Bo are talking about where to go for dinner. ",polarquestion:"“Should we book that restaurant?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s expensive.”"},{Item:3,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Leo",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Leo and Mia enjoy busy and energetic spots for their dates.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the new café downtown?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s crowded.”"},{Item:3,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Leo",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Leo and Mia prefer quiet places when they go on dates.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the new café downtown?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s crowded.”"},{Item:3,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Leo",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Leo and Mia are debating where to go for coffee. ",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the new café downtown?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s crowded.”"},{Item:4,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Anna",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Anna and Mia love spicy food and always go for it.",polarquestion:"“Should we order the special?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s spicy.”"},{Item:4,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Anna",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Anna and Mia both can’t handle spicy dishes.",polarquestion:"“Should we order the special?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s spicy.”"},{Item:4,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Anna",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Anna and Mia are debating what to order for dinner.",polarquestion:"“Should we order the special?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s spicy.”"},{Item:5,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Dan",speaker2:"Alex",contextsentence:"Dan and Alex live approximately 10 minutes away from the train station.",polarquestion:"“Should we go now?”",indirectanswer:"“The train leaves in ten minutes.”"},{Item:5,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Dan",speaker2:"Alex",contextsentence:"Dan and Alex live directly next to the train station - only a minute away.",polarquestion:"“Should we go now?”",indirectanswer:"“The train leaves in ten minutes.”"},{Item:5,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Dan",speaker2:"Alex",contextsentence:"Dan and Alex are talking about when to leave for the train. ",polarquestion:"“Should we go now?”",indirectanswer:"“The train leaves in ten minutes.”"},{Item:6,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Charlie",speaker2:"Millie",contextsentence:"Charlie and Millie are throwing a party together and want to invite someone who will create a lively atmosphere.",polarquestion:"“Should we invite Paul?”",indirectanswer:"“He’s very talkative.”"},{Item:6,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Charlie",speaker2:"Millie",contextsentence:"Charlie and Millie are throwing a dinner party together and want a calm atmosphere.",polarquestion:"“Should we invite Paul?”",indirectanswer:"“He’s very talkative.”"},{Item:6,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Charlie",speaker2:"Millie",contextsentence:"Charlie and Millie are debating whether or not to invite Paul. ",polarquestion:"“Should we invite Paul?”",indirectanswer:"“He’s very talkative.”"},{Item:7,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"John",speaker2:"Emma",contextsentence:"John and Emma are skiers and love fresh snow when they go skiing together.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the mountains this weekend?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s snowing.”"},{Item:7,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"John",speaker2:"Emma",contextsentence:"John and Emma dislike slippery trails on their weekly hikes.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the mountains this weekend?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s snowing.”"},{Item:7,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"John",speaker2:"Emma",contextsentence:"John and Emma are discussing their weekend plans.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to the mountains this weekend?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s snowing.”"},{Item:8,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Peter",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Peter and Anna enjoy museums and always appreciate a good deal.",polarquestion:"“Should we visit the museum?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s free today.”"},{Item:8,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Peter",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Peter  and Anna only like museums when they’re quiet and empty. ",polarquestion:"“Should we visit the museum?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s free today.”"},{Item:8,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Peter",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Peter and Anna are talking about what to do today.",polarquestion:"“Should we visit the museum?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s free today.”"},{Item:9,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Kim",speaker2:"Eva",contextsentence:"Kim and Eva enjoy modern art together.",polarquestion:"“Should we visit the new gallery?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s all contemporary pieces.”"},{Item:9,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Kim",speaker2:"Eva",contextsentence:"Kim and Eva only like classical art.",polarquestion:"“Should we visit the new gallery?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s all contemporary pieces.”"},{Item:9,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Kim",speaker2:"Eva",contextsentence:"Kim and Eva are discussing which gallery to visit.",polarquestion:"“Should we visit the new gallery?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s all contemporary pieces.”"},{Item:10,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Jamie",speaker2:"Tina",contextsentence:"Jamie and Tina like the convenience of central locations when they go on vacation together.",polarquestion:"“Should we book this hotel?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s near the main road.”"},{Item:10,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Jamie",speaker2:"Tina",contextsentence:"Jamie and Tina like sleeping in silence on their vacation.",polarquestion:"“Should we book this hotel?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s near the main road.”"},{Item:10,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Jamie",speaker2:"Tina",contextsentence:"Jamie and Tina are booking a hotel for their next trip. ",polarquestion:"“Should we book this hotel?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s near the main road.”"},{Item:11,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Tom",speaker2:"Lily",contextsentence:"Tom and Lily always celebrate family events together. ",polarquestion:"“Should we visit your parents this weekend?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s their anniversary.”"},{Item:11,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Tom",speaker2:"Lily",contextsentence:"Lily’s parents always spend their anniversaries alone and Tom and Lily are aware of that.",polarquestion:"“Should we visit your parents this weekend?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s their anniversary.”"},{Item:11,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Tom",speaker2:"Lily",contextsentence:"Tom and Lily are considering visiting Lily’s parents over the weekend.",polarquestion:"“Should we visit your parents this weekend?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s their anniversary.”"},{Item:12,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Peter",speaker2:"Laura",contextsentence:"Peter and Laura’s dog loves attention from people.",polarquestion:"“Should we bring the dog?”",indirectanswer:"“There will be a lot of people there.”"},{Item:12,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Peter",speaker2:"Laura",contextsentence:"Peter and Laura’s dog gets very nervous around crowds.",polarquestion:"“Should we bring the dog?”",indirectanswer:"“There will be a lot of people there.”"},{Item:12,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Peter",speaker2:"Laura",contextsentence:"Peter and Laura are considering bringing their dog to an event. ",polarquestion:"“Should we bring the dog?”",indirectanswer:"“There will be a lot of people there.”"},{Item:13,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Paul",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Paul and Anna love watching scary movies together.",polarquestion:"“Should we watch the horror movie?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s supposed to be really scary.”"},{Item:13,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Paul",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Paul and Anna get nightmares very easily.",polarquestion:"“Should we watch the horror movie?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s supposed to be really scary.”"},{Item:13,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Paul",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Paul and Anna are trying to find a movie to watch together. ",polarquestion:"“Should we watch the horror movie?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s supposed to be really scary.”"},{Item:14,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Lina",speaker2:"Sarah",contextsentence:"Lina and Sarah’s trip is coming up soon and they need to book their flights before they get too expensive.",polarquestion:"“Should we book the flight now?",indirectanswer:"“The prices fluctuate daily.”"},{Item:14,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Lina",speaker2:"Sarah",contextsentence:"Lina and Sarah are planning a trip together and they want to wait for the best flight prices.",polarquestion:"“Should we book the flight now?",indirectanswer:"“The prices fluctuate daily.”"},{Item:14,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Lina",speaker2:"Sarah",contextsentence:"Lina and Sarah are planning a trip together. ",polarquestion:"“Should we book the flight now?",indirectanswer:"“The prices fluctuate daily.”"},{Item:15,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Chris",speaker2:"Lara",contextsentence:"Chris and Lara want to form new healthy routines and start their day energized.",polarquestion:"“Should we join the gym class?”",indirectanswer:"“It starts early in the morning.”"},{Item:15,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Chris",speaker2:"Lara",contextsentence:"Chris and Lara aren’t morning people and don’t like early morning activities.",polarquestion:"“Should we join the gym class?”",indirectanswer:"“It starts early in the morning.”"},{Item:15,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Chris",speaker2:"Lara",contextsentence:"Chris and Lara are deciding when to book a gym class.",polarquestion:"“Should we join the gym class?”",indirectanswer:"“It starts early in the morning.”"},{Item:16,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Tim ",speaker2:"Lars",contextsentence:"Tim and Lars are active people and want a dog that matches their lifestyle.",polarquestion:"“Should we adopt this puppy?”",indirectanswer:"“It's very energetic.”"},{Item:16,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Tim ",speaker2:"Lars",contextsentence:"Tim and Lars are very busy and don’t have time for a high maintenance pet.",polarquestion:"“Should we adopt this puppy?”",indirectanswer:"“It's very energetic.”"},{Item:16,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Tim ",speaker2:"Lars",contextsentence:"Tim and Lars want to adopt a dog.",polarquestion:"“Should we adopt this puppy?”",indirectanswer:"“It's very energetic.”"},{Item:17,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Lisa",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Lisa and Anna know that Lisa is looking for regular social activities.",polarquestion:"“Do you want to join the book club?”",indirectanswer:"“They meet every week.”"},{Item:17,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Lisa",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Lisa and Anna know that Lisa has a really busy schedule. ",polarquestion:"“Do you want to join the book club?”",indirectanswer:"“They meet every week.”"},{Item:17,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Lisa",speaker2:"Anna",contextsentence:"Lisa is considering joining Anna’s book club.",polarquestion:"“Do you want to join the book club?”",indirectanswer:"“They meet every week.”"},{Item:18,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Julia",speaker2:"Mark",contextsentence:"Julia and Mark love being outside and enjoy outdoor events in summer.",polarquestion:"“Should we buy tickets for the music festival?”",indirectanswer:"“It's an outdoor venue.”"},{Item:18,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Julia",speaker2:"Mark",contextsentence:"Julia and Mark don’t enjoy outdoor events because of the risk of rain.",polarquestion:"“Should we buy tickets for the music festival?”",indirectanswer:"“It's an outdoor venue.”"},{Item:18,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Julia",speaker2:"Mark",contextsentence:"Julia and Mark are looking at concert options.",polarquestion:"“Should we buy tickets for the music festival?”",indirectanswer:"“It's an outdoor venue.”"},{Item:19,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Sophie",speaker2:"Dan",contextsentence:"Sophie and Dan are looking for an apartment with good views.",polarquestion:"“Should we rent the apartment with the view?”",indirectanswer:"“It's on the top floor.”"},{Item:19,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Sophie",speaker2:"Dan",contextsentence:"Sophie and Dan don’t like taking many stairs. ",polarquestion:"“Should we rent the apartment with the view?”",indirectanswer:"“It's on the top floor.”"},{Item:19,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Sophie",speaker2:"Dan",contextsentence:"Sophie and Dan are moving and debating which apartment to get. ",polarquestion:"“Should we rent the apartment with the view?”",indirectanswer:"“It's on the top floor.”"},{Item:20,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Olivia",speaker2:"Ryan",contextsentence:"Olivia and Ryan have been wanting a regular date night activity.",polarquestion:"“Should we sign up for the cooking class?”",indirectanswer:"“It meets every Tuesday evening.”"},{Item:20,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Olivia",speaker2:"Ryan",contextsentence:"Olivia and Ryan have a dancing class on Tuesday nights.",polarquestion:"“Should we sign up for the cooking class?”",indirectanswer:"“It meets every Tuesday evening.”"},{Item:20,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Olivia",speaker2:"Ryan",contextsentence:"Olivia and Ryan are thinking of new activities to do.",polarquestion:"“Should we sign up for the cooking class?”",indirectanswer:"“It meets every Tuesday evening.”"},{Item:21,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Lisa",speaker2:"Tom",contextsentence:"Lisa and Tom are active people and enjoy going on long walks.",polarquestion:"“Should we walk to the restaurant?”",indirectanswer:"“It's about two miles away.”\""},{Item:21,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Lisa",speaker2:"Tom",contextsentence:"Lisa and Tom both have bad knees.",polarquestion:"“Should we walk to the restaurant?”",indirectanswer:"“It's about two miles away.”"},{Item:21,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Lisa",speaker2:"Tom",contextsentence:"Lisa and Tom are deciding how to get to dinner.",polarquestion:"“Should we walk to the restaurant?”",indirectanswer:"“It's about two miles away.”"},{Item:22,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Matt",speaker2:"Karl",contextsentence:"Matt and Karl have been working since 7am already.",polarquestion:"“Should we take a lunch break now?”",indirectanswer:"“The clock just struck noon.”"},{Item:22,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Matt",speaker2:"Karl",contextsentence:"Matt and Karl want to get as much work done as they can before they take a lunch break.",polarquestion:"“Should we take a lunch break now?”",indirectanswer:"“The clock just struck noon.”"},{Item:22,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Matt",speaker2:"Karl",contextsentence:"Matt and Karl are talking about when to take a break.",polarquestion:"“Should we take a lunch break now?”",indirectanswer:"“The clock just struck noon.”"},{Item:23,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Amy",speaker2:"Paula",contextsentence:"Amy and Paula want to see every art exhibit in the city. ",polarquestion:"“Should we go to that art exhibit?”",indirectanswer:"“It closes this weekend.”"},{Item:23,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Amy",speaker2:"Paula",contextsentence:"Amy and Paula are very busy this week.",polarquestion:"“Should we go to that art exhibit?”",indirectanswer:"“It closes this weekend.”"},{Item:23,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Amy",speaker2:"Paula",contextsentence:"Amy and Paula are talking about weekend activities. ",polarquestion:"“Should we go to that art exhibit?”",indirectanswer:"“It closes this weekend.”"},{Item:24,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Ally",speaker2:"Jane",contextsentence:"Ally and Jane have a ritual of always drinking wine on Tuesdays. ",polarquestion:"“Do you want to share a bottle of wine?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s Tuesday evening.”"},{Item:24,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Ally",speaker2:"Jane",contextsentence:"Ally and Jane have to work early on Wednesday morning.",polarquestion:"“Do you want to share a bottle of wine?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s Tuesday evening.”"},{Item:24,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Ally",speaker2:"Jane",contextsentence:"Ally and Jane are debating what drinks to order.",polarquestion:"“Do you want to share a bottle of wine?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s Tuesday evening.”"},{Item:25,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Abby",speaker2:"Marc",contextsentence:"Abby and Marc both love reading all kinds of romance novels.",polarquestion:"“Do you want to borrow the book from me?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s a romance novel.”"},{Item:25,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Abby",speaker2:"Marc",contextsentence:"Abby and Marc both know that Marc hates romance novels.",polarquestion:"“Do you want to borrow the book from me?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s a romance novel.”"},{Item:25,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Abby",speaker2:"Marc",contextsentence:"Amy and Marc are talking about books.",polarquestion:"“Do you want to borrow the book from me?”",indirectanswer:"“It’s a romance novel.”"},{Item:26,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Lilly",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Lilly and Mia both know that Martin goes silent when he is angry at someone.",polarquestion:"“Do you think Martin is mad at me?”",indirectanswer:"“He was quiet today.”"},{Item:26,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Lilly",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Lilly and Mia both know that Martin usually shouts very loudly when he is angry at someone.",polarquestion:"“Do you think Martin is mad at me?”",indirectanswer:"“He was quiet today.”"},{Item:26,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Lilly",speaker2:"Mia",contextsentence:"Lilly and Mia are talking about their friend Martin.",polarquestion:"“Do you think Martin is mad at me?”",indirectanswer:"“He was quiet today.”"},{Item:27,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Polly",speaker2:"Tim",contextsentence:"Polly and Tim know that Sarah tends to stay late when she’s passionate about her work.",polarquestion:"“Does Sarah like her new job?”",indirectanswer:"“She’s been working late every night.”"},{Item:27,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Polly",speaker2:"Tim",contextsentence:"Polly and Tim know that Sarah only works late when she’s stressed.",polarquestion:"“Does Sarah like her new job?”",indirectanswer:"“She’s been working late every night.”"},{Item:27,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Polly",speaker2:"Tim",contextsentence:"Polly and Tim know that Sarah started a new position last month.",polarquestion:"“Does Sarah like her new job?”",indirectanswer:"“She’s been working late every night.”"},{Item:28,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Ben",speaker2:"Max",contextsentence:"Ben and Max’s boss always brings baked goods when she is happy.",polarquestion:"“Is the boss in a good mood today?”",indirectanswer:"“She brought donuts for everyone.”"},{Item:28,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Ben",speaker2:"Max",contextsentence:"Ben and Max’s boss only brings baked goods when she is trying to apologize for bad news.",polarquestion:"“Is the boss in a good mood today?”",indirectanswer:"“She brought donuts for everyone.”"},{Item:28,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Ben",speaker2:"Max",contextsentence:"Ben and Max are talking about their boss.",polarquestion:"“Is the boss in a good mood today?”",indirectanswer:"“She brought donuts for everyone.”"},{Item:29,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Anna",speaker2:"David",contextsentence:"Anna and David know detailed feedback means that the reader resonated with the material.",polarquestion:"“Did Professor Chen like your thesis proposal?”",indirectanswer:"“She gave me three pages of comments.”"},{Item:29,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Anna",speaker2:"David",contextsentence:"Anna and David think excessive comments signal major problems.",polarquestion:"“Did Professor Chen like your thesis proposal?”",indirectanswer:"“She gave me three pages of comments.”"},{Item:29,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Anna",speaker2:"David",contextsentence:"Anna and David are talking about David’s thesis meeting.",polarquestion:"“Did Professor Chen like your thesis proposal?”",indirectanswer:"“She gave me three pages of comments.”"},{Item:30,"Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Erik",speaker2:"Meredith",contextsentence:"Erik and Meredith love Jake's spacious house and great parties.",polarquestion:"“Are you going to the party on Saturday?”",indirectanswer:"“It's at Jake's place.”"},{Item:30,"Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Erik",speaker2:"Meredith",contextsentence:"Erik and Meredith find Jake's parties awkward and uncomfortable.",polarquestion:"“Are you going to the party on Saturday?”",indirectanswer:"“It's at Jake's place.”"},{Item:30,"Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Erik",speaker2:"Meredith",contextsentence:"Erik and Meredith are discussing weekend plans.",polarquestion:"“Are you going to the party on Saturday?”",indirectanswer:"“It's at Jake's place.”"}]},5851:function(e){e.exports=[{Item:"attn1","Context Type":"positive",speaker1:"Nina",speaker2:"Sam",contextsentence:"On this trial please select the definitely yes rating.",polarquestion:"“Should we get coffee?”",indirectanswer:"“It has caffeine in it.”"},{Item:"attn2","Context Type":"negative",speaker1:"Olivia",speaker2:"Katie",contextsentence:"Olivia and Katie are planning to go to the cinema.",polarquestion:"On this trial please select the middle rating.",indirectanswer:"“It’s an action movie.”"},{Item:"attn3","Context Type":"neutral",speaker1:"Peter",speaker2:"Kyle",contextsentence:"Peter and Kyle want to decide what to buy at the grocery store.",polarquestion:"“Should we get the canned tomatoes?”",indirectanswer:"On this trial please select the definitely no rating."}]}},t={};function n(a){var o=t[a];if(void 0!==o)return o.exports;var r=t[a]={id:a,loaded:!1,exports:{}};return e[a].call(r.exports,r,r.exports,n),r.loaded=!0,r.exports}n.m=e,function(){var e=[];n.O=function(t,a,o,r){if(!a){var i=1/0;for(c=0;c<e.length;c++){a=e[c][0],o=e[c][1],r=e[c][2];for(var s=!0,l=0;l<a.length;l++)(!1&r||i>=r)&&Object.keys(n.O).every(function(e){return n.O[e](a[l])})?a.splice(l--,1):(s=!1,r<i&&(i=r));if(s){e.splice(c--,1);var p=o();void 0!==p&&(t=p)}}return t}r=r||0;for(var c=e.length;c>0&&e[c-1][2]>r;c--)e[c]=e[c-1];e[c]=[a,o,r]}}(),function(){n.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return n.d(t,{a:t}),t}}(),function(){n.d=function(e,t){for(var a in t)n.o(t,a)&&!n.o(e,a)&&Object.defineProperty(e,a,{enumerable:!0,get:t[a]})}}(),function(){n.f={},n.e=function(e){return Promise.all(Object.keys(n.f).reduce(function(t,a){return n.f[a](e,t),t},[]))}}(),function(){n.u=function(e){return"js/"+e+".58068b7f.js"}}(),function(){n.miniCssF=function(e){}}(),function(){n.g=function(){if("object"===typeof globalThis)return globalThis;try{return this||new Function("return this")()}catch(e){if("object"===typeof window)return window}}()}(),function(){n.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)}}(),function(){var e={},t="indicom:";n.l=function(a,o,r,i){if(e[a])e[a].push(o);else{var s,l;if(void 0!==r)for(var p=document.getElementsByTagName("script"),c=0;c<p.length;c++){var d=p[c];if(d.getAttribute("src")==a||d.getAttribute("data-webpack")==t+r){s=d;break}}s||(l=!0,s=document.createElement("script"),s.charset="utf-8",n.nc&&s.setAttribute("nonce",n.nc),s.setAttribute("data-webpack",t+r),s.src=a),e[a]=[o];var u=function(t,n){s.onerror=s.onload=null,clearTimeout(h);var o=e[a];if(delete e[a],s.parentNode&&s.parentNode.removeChild(s),o&&o.forEach(function(e){return e(n)}),t)return t(n)},h=setTimeout(u.bind(null,void 0,{type:"timeout",target:s}),12e4);s.onerror=u.bind(null,s.onerror),s.onload=u.bind(null,s.onload),l&&document.head.appendChild(s)}}}(),function(){n.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})}}(),function(){n.nmd=function(e){return e.paths=[],e.children||(e.children=[]),e}}(),function(){n.p="/A1-indicom/experiments/A1-Indicom-pilot1/"}(),function(){var e={524:0};n.f.j=function(t,a){var o=n.o(e,t)?e[t]:void 0;if(0!==o)if(o)a.push(o[2]);else{var r=new Promise(function(n,a){o=e[t]=[n,a]});a.push(o[2]=r);var i=n.p+n.u(t),s=new Error,l=function(a){if(n.o(e,t)&&(o=e[t],0!==o&&(e[t]=void 0),o)){var r=a&&("load"===a.type?"missing":a.type),i=a&&a.target&&a.target.src;s.message="Loading chunk "+t+" failed.\n("+r+": "+i+")",s.name="ChunkLoadError",s.type=r,s.request=i,o[1](s)}};n.l(i,l,"chunk-"+t,t)}},n.O.j=function(t){return 0===e[t]};var t=function(t,a){var o,r,i=a[0],s=a[1],l=a[2],p=0;if(i.some(function(t){return 0!==e[t]})){for(o in s)n.o(s,o)&&(n.m[o]=s[o]);if(l)var c=l(n)}for(t&&t(a);p<i.length;p++)r=i[p],n.o(e,r)&&e[r]&&e[r][0](),e[r]=0;return n.O(c)},a=self["webpackChunkindicom"]=self["webpackChunkindicom"]||[];a.forEach(t.bind(null,0)),a.push=t.bind(null,a.push.bind(a))}();var a=n.O(void 0,[504],function(){return n(3762)});a=n.O(a)})();
//# sourceMappingURL=app.c4a48ca2.js.map